Look at y'all.
It's good to see you.
>> When you left last year, did you think
this would ever be possible coming back
here?
>> Uh, anything's possible, man. So, I
think it's it's uh always, man. I don't
think I ever
really doubt or think too much about
anything, you know. It's I love my time
here. So, it was
>> Yeah.
>> Obviously, you're excited to to [snorts]
be back, you know, when this opportunity
start to become a little bit more
realistic. Uh what made this the right
choice for you?
[sighs]
[gasps]
>> Cuz it makes it makes me happy, man.
Makes my heart happy. Um
it tells you it's right, man. You listen
to your heart, it tells you it's right,
you know. So, it's it's I'm happy to be
here. I'm happy I'm happy my family's
here. Um
it's amazing, man, to be here. And um
it's truly a blessing.
>> What was the family's reaction?
>> You can only imagine, man. They're
juiced. They're ready. And um
it's something that I don't even know if
it was on their mind, you know, a week
ago. and and didn't know if it was if it
was a real thing to believe in. You
know, that we don't you know, at that
time, you don't know where you're going
to be, right? It's a it's a crazy world,
man. It's a crazy business, you know,
and uh I'm blessed to be part of it, for
sure.
>> How different is Roy Lopez now versus
the Royal Lopez that walked out of this
building a little over a year ago?
>> Oh, I've grown. I've grown so much
mentally as a man, um, as a human, as a
follower of Christ. Um,
but I promise you I'm the same me, man.
You can probably tell by the way I
walked in here. I'm the same me. I
always be me. Um,
I I have grown though, man. And so, I
can't wait to see the guys. And I I I
literally can't wait. And um, you know,
thank you to to Michael
Monty, Coach Laflur,
Nick, everybody, man. I can't I can't
wait to see everybody and strap it up
again. And it's a blessing. It's a
blessing.
>> Is it weird coming back with a new head
[clears throat] coach after you were
here with the older team and everything?
>> Weird? No. Um,
it's exciting though. You know, I know
he's excited. Um, yeah, this is awesome
for him and um to be a part of it, to be
a part of his, you know, his first year
and it's it's amazing, you know, cuz I
know he's hungry. He's hungry like all
of us, right? And and you know, as a kid
from the city, it's it's all you want,
man, is an opportunity, you know, so I'm
blessed to be here. I'm hungry to to get
us going where we need to go. And it's
this is amazing. and and that's why I'm
blessed to be part of the room that I
am, you know. So,
>> some guys in that room that that you
texted or that text you kind of as the
news happens excited to catch up with
>> Oh, yeah. Um Dante and Dro were pretty
pretty quick if you if you could
imagine. Uh Dro's my guy, man. So, he
was pretty pumped. [laughter]
Uh, so I can't wait to see them and um I
can't wait to see LJ, you know, I can't
wait to see see a bunch of guys and and
meet, you know, meet the new faces as
well. And um, you know, I can only
imagine that, you know, when we all get
together and and we all get back in the
same room that, you know, everybody's
going to have a story about Roy and
whether they're true or not where they
come from Dro, but Dro probably makes up
half the stories he tells. But it's uh
you know I I can't wait. It's awesome.
>> What do you feel like works for you
playing's
defense here?
>> I think the biggest thing that I
appreciated him for when I was here and
when I wasn't here and coming back and
everything, the first thing that comes
to my mind is just his mental. He's he's
so smart. He's so smart. He knows the
game of ball. He knows preparation. He
knows day of. He knows not blinking in
adversity and through his tone of voice,
through his belief in you and you he
wants to be the dog. He wants to be the
big dog in the arena, right? Like and so
when you play for a guy like that and
you're surrounded with guys that same
mentality, it's it's exciting to be out
there, man. It's excited to buckle your
helmet up and you know and uh last time
I was here, Mac wasn't the green dot,
but you know, I can only imagine him
with the green dot, right? Like it's
it's uh when you're when you're in a
room like that and and you got Buddha
back there. I I think the last time I
was I was here I said the same thing,
man. It's nothing like getting in the
huddle and you see Buddha back there
like you're good. You're good. Like so I
know I kind of veered off your question,
but um that his mental his his delivery
his his messes his belief in you like
that's that's why you play for Nick
Rollins.
>> So much love from back here. Did you
keep up the Cardinals at all last year?
>> Come on, man.
I'm from here. Of course I did.
[laughter]
Of course I did. You know, of course I
did. Yes.
>> You mentioned the areas you kind of grew
kind of off the field, on the field,
what was the biggest stuff you feel like
took away from your
>> Yeah. I think the biggest thing was
probably um
taking advantage of your opportunities,
right? And some games I'm I'm not
getting the snap count I want or
whatever it was, right? or getting the
look I want or and just being able to
all excuses got to go out the door,
right? And and I think the biggest thing
was was preparation and understanding
when I get in, it's on, right? It's on.
And and if I get this play call against
this play and I get this formation
against this play call, it's on, right?
and just kind of, you know, preparing
and seeing things before they happen.
And and when they do, it's like you kind
of get the the look in your in in your
mirror, you get the look in your visor.
You kind of see yourself and be like,
"Yeah, you saw that on Wednesday. You
saw that on Thursday, right?" And it's
it's just a a credit to yourself. And
also the room I was in out there. It
was, you know, it's it's I'm so grateful
for my time out there. It was amazing.
It was the people I worked with, the
people I played with, the coaches,
everybody. And I learned a lot in a year
and one of those things where you know
when they do happen on Sunday you get to
the sideline you look at them like yeah
that's exactly what you think it was is
what I thought it was and then it came
true and now we're laughing right like
it's one of those things it was amazing
to shovel snow anymore.
>> Yeah that was crazy.
Shoveling snow is underrated. That is
man that was not Yeah.
It was cool though. It is cool. Um, I
feel like it's a cool thing to do. Like
if you got like a son and be like cold
shovel, snow, like that's cool. That's
cool. Um, but if you ask my lady, I
didn't do it too much. I didn't do it
too often, but I say I did all the time,
but uh
the I was in a good community, so
sometimes they shoveled the sidewalk for
me. Um, so that was cool. But I learned
about salting snow. Um,
yeah, it was cool.
>> Did you push to come back?
>> Um,
did I push to come back?
I thought I had a great year in Detroit.
And the biggest thing for me is my
mental happiness,
my true heart and soul happiness.
and
praying on it
and when like it hits you that that's
that's where you're going to go wherever
it was going to be. And
so when it became this place as the
answer, it was
boom. Like heart was instantly happy.
Mental was instantly good. Peace
like I was good. I was happy, right? It
was one of those things where I knew I
just did it a year ago going into frey
and it was the same thing a year ago was
okay if that's where I'm going. And it
made my heart happy, made my mental
happy, gave me peace. That's where I'm
going, right? And to be here a year
later and I'm back in this room, you
talking to y'all like you guys know what
I stand for. You guys know what I come
from. And um
so yeah, when when the decision was
made, it was it was made mentally from
within. And you know, it's it's great.
>> How did or how will your family
celebrate this? What are the plans to
celebrate or what have you already done
with the family to market.
>> No, we got a foundation meeting coming
up on Saturday, so that's when I'll see
everybody. Um, but I know they're
juiced. I know they're pumped.
Everybody's reached out and um I'm
excited. I'm I'm I'm truly grateful and
um
it's it's it's something that comes up
kind of sidetracking off your question.
Sorry. Something that comes up to my
mind is um that I hold close to to my
heart memories growing up. It's when you
go to wrestling tournaments or you go to
uh events or you go see your mom at work
or whatever it is, right? You you do
those things and
and like you're you're at the wrestling
term and a guy comes up like, "What's
up, bro? What's up, man?" Talking to
your dad and you're just kind of
standing there like, "Bro, like, I need
a snack, bro." Like, and the guy comes
up to you like kind of nods you on the
head like, "Your dad was a beast, bro.
Your dad was a beast." Right? Like,
that's cool. That's cool. Yeah.
Whatever.
whatever, right? And then you go to your
mom's work and they're like, "Your mom's
a beast. Like, she's amazing. She's
amazing at what she does." Like
those things, right? Those things you
remember. You meet your uncle's friends.
And bro, your uncle's hilarious. He's
amazing. It's the guy right there.
That's my best friend. He's my best
friend. He's my best friend first. Okay.
And same thing, it goes for my sisters
and my cousins. And your nana is an
angel. Yeah, I know. My nana is an
angel. Like
your thought was one of the greatest
police officers in the city of Phoenix.
Thank you. He earned that. He earned
that. And
the other day I was working out.
[clears throat] I was working out and
I trained I trained my cousin and uh so
we're went to the raft wrestling.
And so somehow I thought I could still
wrestle. I still can, by the way, in
case you guys wonder. I'm gonna check
out Raph Wrestling when I'm done. Um,
and I got a black eye, by the way. He
headbutted me and
so I got a black eye and I'm I'm lifting
and we're doing legs and I was
squatting. I had a lot of weight on
there. I look at my lady and she's seven
months pregnant. And I was like, "My boy
going to know about me."
Like
someone's gonna tell my boy, "Your dad
was a beast, bro. Even if they're lying,
you know, even if it's one of y'all
sitting here, you know what I'm saying?
Like just lie real quick for him, for
me." Um,
like that's that's that's what means
something to me. Like
because my father created a legacy. My
dad did, my uncles did, and uh my
cousins are still. And um to be here in
front of y'all, bro, I wearing a shirt
that says it takes a village. It truly
does. And um I know I'm blessed and
fortunate to be in my position, have my
village, and uh it's something that we
will express at my I have a youth camp
coming up on March 28th that my village
is big and it's it's willing to be
somebody else's village and and more
than willing to reach out and show love
and show how we did it and just to give
a smile, man. So, I veered from your
question, but you made me think of
something.
>> Yeah. So, yeah, we got a we got a
meeting coming up. Yeah. So, yeah.
Appreciate y'all, man.
Welcome back. Thank Thank you.